Hi folks!

I am **HEMNATH**

29 year old Profoundly skilled designer with high proficiency in visual design.

Visual Designer

With 7.5 years of Design Experience











hemnathharidass

Professional Skills



User Experience Designer

Understanding User needs / Competitor Analysis / Creating Persona / Information Architecture / Creating Wire frames.



User Interface Designer

Defining Color themes / Typography / Icons / Illustrations / UI screens / Marketing collaterals.



User Interface Developer

Converting PSD to Html Layout / image optimization / CSS styling / Creating Font icons / Animation using Css and jQuery.

Software Skills















Experience Summary

Studio 45



Studio 45

2009 - 2011

Designer

Roles & Responsiblities

Creating Flash Templates, Illustrations, Website, 2d animations, Marketing collaterals, Logo design, Icons, Brouchers, Posters, Corporate presentations, E- Learning modules etc.





Element K

2011 - 2012

Art & Media Developer

Roles & Responsiblities

Flash Templates, Icons,
Illustrations, E - Learning,
2d animations, Image
Optimization, Localization,
Flash Presentations, Mailer
designs etc.





Object Frontier Software

2012 - 2015

Design Engineer

Roles & Responsiblities

Marketing collaterals,
Website design, E- Books,
Power Point Presentations,
User experience design,
Mailers, Posters, Font icons,
User Interface design, Html
conversion, Css stylings,
Media query etc.





Zoho Corporation

2015 - Till Date

Visual Designer

Roles & Responsiblities

User experience design,
User Interface design, Html
conversion, Css styling,
E- Books, Mailer template,
SVG illustrations, Font icons,
Css animations, Front end
bug fixing etc.

Education

B.Sc Visual Communication

DGVC College (Chennai)

2006 - 2009

ST Marys Matric

Higher Secondry School (Chennai)



IFX certification in Flash

Hobbies & Intrests







Sketching

Photography

Art & Crafts

Personal Info

Name **Hemnath.H**

Gender Male

Date of birth **07 september 1988**

Marital Status Married

Location Chennai

Contact Info



9791106538



hemnath21@gmail.com